SHARON MACUGU

Data Analyst & Administration

Contact

Address

Nairobi, 14169, 00100

Phone

+254740645674

E-mail

sharonmacugu@gmail.com

Skills

Data Manipulation

Very Good

Spreadsheet management

Good

Office administration

Very Good

Statistical data gathering

Good

Proficient in SPSS and Stata

Very Good

Analyzing trends

Languages

English

Excellent

Kiswahili

Detailed analyst and administrator with advanced skills in records management and data analysis. Attentive when handling incoming records, collecting data, analyzing trends and managing administrative works. Analytical and critical thinker with excellent judgment and expertise in MS Office, SPSS

Work History

2021-09 -Current

Administrative Assistant

Ramsa Limited, Nairobi, Nairobi

- Supported efficient meetings by organizing spaces and materials, documenting discussions and distributing meeting notes.
- Developed and updated spreadsheets and databases to track, analyze and report on performance and sales data.
- Offered office-wide software support and training, troubleshooting issues and optimizing usage.
- Scheduled an average of 10 office meetings and client appointments for staff teams per day
- Answered an average of 20 multi-line phone system, routing calls, delivering messages to staff and greeting visitors.

2021-04 -2021-09

Data Analyst Intern

Brandscope Limited, Nairobi, Nairobi

- Completed data cleaning and data validation of existing 30 spreadsheets to promote robust data management platform, resulting in accurate data analysis and entry.
- Cleaned up and backed up data to maintain data integrity during extraction, manipulation and processing.
- Presented reports to clients and teammates regarding project progress and results.

Education

2018-05 -Current Bachelor of Science: Mathematics - Statistics

Excellent

French

Average

Catholic University of Eastern Africa - Nairobi

Completed and competently able to apply
 Statistical Methods and Survey Techniques to a wide
 range of practical problems, analyze large data sets
 using Statistical Computing Techniques and employ
 Statistical Methods necessary in making
 evidence-based decisions.

2018-01 -2018-04

Certificate: Computer Applications (CCA)

KCA University - Nairobi

 Relevant Coursework Completed: Computer Applications; Windows, Microsoft Productivity Applications, Basic Computer Maintenance